Egypt
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Egypt
2.1.2.1.3
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1342
- Egypt, 2.1.2.1.3
  - Sailboat in Suez Canal at sunset, 1918; 6; 3-7; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - View of three pyramids from airplane (aerial view), 1918; 7; 3-15; 3x4 color (Box 1342)
  - View of three pyramids from airplane (aerial view), 1918; 8; 3-15; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Heliopolis, 1918; 9; 3-19; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Barracks of Egyptian army from airplane (aerial view), 1918; 10; 3-21; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - View of Egypt from airplane, best view (aerial view), 1918; 11; 3-22; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Lowell Thomas on camel in front of Sphinx, paying Egyptian, Great Pyramid of Giza in background, 1918; 12; 3-28; 3x4 color (Box 1342)
  - Lowell Thomas on camel in front of Sphinx, paying Egyptian, Great Pyramid of Giza in background, 1918; 13; 3-28; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Cheops pyramid from airplane (aerial view), 1918; 14; 3-30; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Pyramid, palm trees, and men sitting in the foreground, 1918; 15; 3-33; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Pyramid and double palm trees in center, 1918; 16; 3-35; 3x4 color (Box 1342)
  - Pyramid and double palm trees in center, 1918; 17; 3-35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Pyramid and double palm trees in center, 1918; 18; 3-35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Three pyramids of Giza and Sphinx, silhouette, 1918; 19; 3-45; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Veiled girl, full length, 1918; 20; 3-49; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Sphinx head, 1918; 21; 3-51; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Lowell Thomas and Egyptian cobbler, 1918; 22; 3-52; 3x4 color (Box 1342)
  - Four little Armenian children, 1918; 23; 3-54; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Armenian men and old woman, 1918; 24; 3-57; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Armenian men and old woman, 1918; 25; 3-57; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Armenian men and old woman, 1918; 26; 3-57; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Armenian men and old woman, 1918; 27; 3-57; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Old Armenian, 1918; 28; 3-58; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Old Armenian, 1918; 29; 3-58; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Old Armenian, 1918; 30; 3-58; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Australian soldiers watch Armenian women sew at a refugee camp, 1918; 31; 3-60; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Australian soldiers watch Armenian women sew at a refugee camp, 1918; 32; 3-60; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Two Australian soldiers watch Armenian women sew at a refugee camp, 1918; 33; 3-60; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Sailboat in Suez Canal at sunset, best view, 1918; 34; 3-72; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Sailboat in Suez Canal at sunset, best view, 1918; 35; 3-72; 3x4 b&w (Box 1342)
  - Well of Moses, Lowell Thomas and three soldiers eating lunch, 1918; 36; 3-76; 3x4 color (Box 1342)
  Box 1343
- Egypt, 2.1.2.1.3
  - Well of Moses, Lowell Thomas and three soldiers eating lunch, 1918; 1; 3-76; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - British soldier lying under palm tree, 1918; 2; 3-77; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Pyramid, double palm tree, no people, 1918; 3; 3-84; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - Lowell Thomas on donkey, palace of governor in Khartown, 1918; 4; 3-96; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Omdurman, panorama, 1918; 5; 3-98; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Omdurman, panorama, 1918; 6; 3-98; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - A Sudan train, 1918; 7; 3-103; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Sudan sandstorm [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: sand storm rolling down on Khartoum], 1918; 8; 3-105; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Sudan sandstorm [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: sand storm rolling down on Khartoum], 1918; 9; 3-105; 3x4 color (Box 1343)
  - Sudan sandstorm [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: sand storm rolling down on Khartoum], 1918; 10; 3-105; 3x4 b&w (Box 1343)
  - Tents of troops arriving from India, Suez, 1918; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1343)